And corn meal gets sticky easily.
So, ahh, pour give it on there and then I will rub it all around, and I 'm using a very white shallow dish.
Is getting on it and I dripped it over there, we'll get that later.
All around, yeah, I put plenty in there.
that's good.
Alright, I cleared out all edges.
And it doesn't matter what's this corn bread looks like.
It's going to be broken up and throw into our bigger dish anyway, so it doesn't matter what it looks like.
and I like the shallow dish, the big shallow dish because it get baked so quickly so I don't have to wait that long for corn bread to cook.
It doesn't take that long anyway, but just is so nice and fast.
I'm going to set that aside now that is all grease up and let's turn to our ingredients.
I need two cups of corn meal.
They make yellow corn meal and white corn meal.
I have yellow.
Ahh, recipes can vary between the yellow and the white, so pay attention to that.
Ahh, most times when you just buy the corn meal, it will have the recipe right on the box on how to make the corn bread.
I already put mine in my in my canester, so we'll talk it out together.
I just entered a cup, I couldn't quite figure out.
So I'm going to make sure I got two cups of this in there Maybe enough, add a litle bit more because I put in there under a cup both times.
Let's see that's about right and that's it.
Excellent.
That's the start of our corn bread.
Add one big egg, I already have my egg in here.
I'm just going go ahead and get that pour in there.
There we go.
We can put that aside and I do need a cup of more ingredients.
We're gonna start mixing this together before we add everything else